Narrator: 1
Speaker: I enjoy reading in bed.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: Have you finished tidying your room?
Narrator: 3
Speaker: I want to go on working until I’m seventy.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: I hate being late when I’m meeting someone.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: I like having breakfast in a café.
Narrator: 6
Speaker: I love waking up on a sunny morning.
Narrator: 7
Speaker: I don’t mind doing the ironing. It’s quite relaxing.
Narrator: 8
Speaker: She spends hours talking on the phone.
Narrator: 9
Speaker: It started raining at five thirty in the morning.
Narrator: 10
Speaker: Please stop making such a noise. I can’t think.
Narrator: 11
Speaker: I don’t feel like cooking today. Let’s go out for lunch.